And when
it gets listed, we will talk about it again. I mean, first of all, let's
bring the stock,
although you are probably late in entering, but
look at Polycap, what a great move,
three big green bars have formed since morning and you are
consolidating a bit, but a great
move here,
it is a stock which has less momentum.
Apart from that, JSPL has brought momentum today, the
metal index has brought it, let's
revisit it once, you will find a good move in the metal index
today, Nifty Metal is
showing you a move of around 1.5% at this time, so it is a
great move here, yesterday's
Tata Chemicals which had the highest decline, there is a
little recovery there now, although it is counter way,
but it is trying a little
to come back to the green,
you will see a little bit there in PFC and
actually on PFC, yesterday it was probably Kavita ji's
yesterday, so it is doing well, at this
time, these are some stocks which are
showing their performance, people are
taking it positively and
Glenmark's news suddenly came in the green,
now he was saying in positive,
understand it a little bit.  It will have to be seen
how the market will understand it. On one hand you are giving 48 million dollars
but on the other hand you are settling
that too with a big company like Mark.
So it had to be seen how the market
will react and now see, there is
good momentum in the stock, it is up by almost 2.5%. Now let's
talk about the stock of D De. Let's go to Sumit
for that. Sumit. Good morning.
Morning. Today there is a lot of action in many stocks here.
News Close was
also one of them where a good move was
seen but let's start
first with the earnings numbers or those
news where you will see the reaction today, it is
up by 9%. So we have Bisleri up by 5%, above the new year.
Aventik's listing yesterday was up by 6%.
This also seems to be doing less.
Look at all the stocks one by one. First ICC
Lombard, where the company's numbers came, they were
seen coming slightly below the expectations
and in Q4 numbers the
figures were slightly below the estimates. The profit is around 39% bigger, Rs
437 crore, the profit of this company came
They increase on the basis of premium income tax. This
12% is big but on a sequential basis, the
numbers here are seen coming from all the dudes. The
combined ratio came around 104% which was
also Hanuman's 10390%
coming around 103 rupees. So this kind of impact has been
seen here. So the
numbers on the overall pick side, why their space
impact, you are seeing here
where one of the company's plants has been
infected by USFD in the company's
sellers will manufacturing facility
and an IR has been issued to the company. The
company has brought the plant here with a clean chit.
You are seeing its reaction
around the bureaucracy.
Som Distillery is working on new highs of the year at
Rs 167-168 and the
interesting part is that the
beer production of this company has started in Karnataka.
Its production has already started in Canada or its plant. We have already
mentioned its presence
in the Karnataka market in the plane of Karnataka.  The market
share is also expanding slowly, there
is expansion in the area as well, plus new units are also
being added, volume is expected to improve here, due to which the
stock is losing 5% in reaction. Avent Tech is
listed yesterday and after the listing, the
details of the blocks that were there yesterday came, after that there are shares,
in this Goldman Sachs Investment has bought 5.5
lakh shares on the strength of 4008 and
in the other portfolio also, along with 3.5 lakh shares yesterday, 7.5
lakh shares have been taken by Goldman Sachs,
so one reaction to this was
200 and 2% up in the stock, due to which
Sumit is doing less.